So when I looked closely at the historical market data,
I finally realized that the entire housing bubble was complete
That is exactly why you failed.
You ignored inflation metrics.
[Spanish (LATAM)]
Al analizar los datos históricos del mercado,
Noté que la burbuja inmobiliaria
estalló. Por eso fracasaste.
Ignoraste las métricas de inflación.
[French (France)]
En examinant
les données historiques du marché,
J'ai compris que la bulle immobilière
était totale. C'est
précisément pour ça que vous avez échoué.
Vous avez ignoré l'inflation.
[German]
Bei der Analyse der historischen Marktdaten
sah ich: Die Immobilienblase
war voll ausgebildet.
Genau deshalb sind Sie gescheitert.
Sie ignorierten Inflationsdaten.
[Italian]
Analizzando nel dettaglio i dati storici
di mercato, Ho finalmente
capito che la bolla immobiliare
era completa. Ecco perché hai fallito.
Hai ignorato i tassi d'inflazione.
[Portuguese (Brazil)]
Ao analisar os dados históricos do mercado,
Notei que a bolha imobiliária era total.
É por isso que você falhou.
Você ignorou métricas da inflação.
[Japanese]
市場の​過去​データを​注視した時、
住宅​バブルが​崩壊したと​気づいたの​です。
だから​あなたは​失敗した。
インフレ​指標を​無視したから​です。
[Mandarin (Simplified)]
当​我​仔细​研究​历史​市场​数据 时，
我​终于​意识​到​整个​房地产​泡沫​已经​ 形成，
这​正是​你​失败的​原因。
你​忽视了​通胀​指标。
[Arabic (Modern Standard)]
عندما دققت في بيانات السوق التاريخية،
أدركت أن فقاعة الإسكان كانت مكتملة.
ولهذا السبب تحديداً فشلت.
لقد تجاهلت مؤشرات التضخم.
[Hindi]
तो जब मैंने बाजार के ऐतिहासिक आंकड़ों
को बारीकी से देखा, तब मुझे एहसास हुआ
कि आवास क्षेत्र का गुब्बारा पूरी तरह
फूल चुका था। इसीलिए आप नाकाम रहे।
आपने मुद्रास्फीति के मानकों की अनदेखी की।
[Russian]
Изучив внимательно исторические
рыночные данные, Я наконец осознал:
пузырь на рынке жилья лопнул.
Именно поэтому вы потерпели неудачу.
Вы игнорировали метрики инфляции.
[Turkish]
Tarihsel piyasa verilerini yakından
incelediğimde, Konut balonunun tamamen
patladığını anladım.
İşte tam da bu yüzden kaybettin.
Enflasyon verilerini görmezden geldin.
[Thai]
พอดู​ข้อมูลตลาด​ย้อนหลัง​ดีๆ
ผม​ถึงรู้​ว่าฟองสบู่​อสังหาฯ​เกิดขึ้น
แล้วนั่นแหละ​เหตุผล​ที่​คุณ​พัง
คุณ​ละเลย​ดัชนีเงินเฟ้อ
[Korean]
과거 시장 데이터를 면밀히 분석했을
때, 부동산 거품이 완전히 끝났음을
깨달았습니다. 그게 바로 당신이 실패한
이유입니다. 인플레이션 지표를 무시했으니까요.
[Swedish]
Vid en närmare granskning
av historisk marknadsdata Insåg jag att
hela bostadsbubblan var total.
Det är precis därför du misslyckades.
Du ignorerade inflationsmåtten.
[Dutch]
Bij nadere blik op de historische marktdata,
besefte ik dat de huizenzeepbel
volledig was. Daarom heb je gefaald.
Je negeerde inflatiecijfers.