What is up, guys? We are live
from the absolute craziest street festival
ever, and the energy
out here is literally
off the charts today.
[Spanish (LATAM)]
¡Hola a todos!
Estamos en vivo desde
el festival callejero
más loco de todos,
y la energía de hoy está
fuera de serie.
[French (France)]
Salut tout le monde!
On est en direct du festival
le plus fou de tous!
L'ambiance est juste
incroyable aujourd'hui.
[German]
Was geht, Leute?
Wir sind live beim
krassesten Straßenfest
überhaupt, und die Stimmung hier
ist heute einfach unbeschreiblich.
[Italian]
Come va, ragazzi? Siamo live
dal festival di strada
più pazzo di sempre,
e l'energia qui oggi
è letteralmente fuori scala.
[Portuguese (Brazil)]
E aí, pessoal! Estamos ao vivo
do festival de rua mais
insano de todos,
e a energia aqui hoje está surreal!
[Japanese]
みんな​調子​どう？
史上​最強に​ヤバい
ストリート​フェスから​生​中継中！
今日の​熱気は​マジで
ありえない​レベルだよ！
[Mandarin (Simplified)]
嘿​大家​好 呀！
我们​正在​史上​最​疯狂
街头​狂欢节​ 现场直播​，
今天​这里的​气氛​简直​嗨​到​爆表！
[Arabic (Modern Standard)]
كيف الحال يا شباب؟
نحن مباشرة من أكثر
مهرجان شوارع جنوناً
على الإطلاق
والطاقة هنا اليوم
خيالية وفوق الوصف
[Hindi]
क्या हाल है, दोस्तों? हम लाइव हैं अब
तक के सबसे धमाकेदार स्ट्रीट फेस्टिवल से,
और आज यहाँ एनर्जी
सच में आसमान छू रही है।
[Russian]
Всем привет!
Мы ведем репортаж
с безумного стрит-фестиваля!
Энергия здесь сегодня
просто зашкаливает!
[Korean]
여러분, 안녕하세요!
지금 역대급으로 미친
거리 축제 현장에
나와 있는데요,
오늘 여기 열기가 진짜
장난이 아닙니다.
[Turkish]
Naber millet?
Şu an gelmiş geçmiş
en çılgın sokak festivalinden
canlı yayındayız, ve buradaki enerji
bugün resmen tavan
yapmış durumda.
[Indonesian]
Apa kabar, guys? Kita lagi live
dari festival jalanan
paling gokil yang pernah
ada, dan energinya
benar-benar gila hari ini!
[Thai]
หวัดดีครับ​ ทุก​คน เรา
ไลฟ์​จากสตรีท​เฟสติวัล
ที่​มันส์สุดยอด​มาก
พลังงาน​ที่นี่​ล้นทะลัก​แบบสุดๆ​วันนี้
[Swedish]
Tjena, allihopa! Vi är live
från den absolut
vildaste gatufestivalen någonsin,
och energin
här ute är helt galen idag.