最神仙​折叠屏​瞬息​满血​急速​闪冲
[Spanish (LATAM)]
Carga ultraveloz
[French (France)]
Pliable de rêve: charge éclair
[German]
Falt-Genie lädt blitzschnell voll
[Italian]
Il pieghevole divino:
ricarica flash istantanea al 100%
[Portuguese (Brazil)]
O dobrável definitivo:
carga flash instantânea a 100%
[Japanese]
まさに​神レベルの、
瞬時に​フル​充電​できる超
高速 フラッシュチャージ！
[Mandarin (Simplified)]
最神仙​折叠屏​瞬息​满血​急速​闪冲
[Arabic (Modern Standard)]
أروع هاتف مطوي
يشحن بلحظة!
[Hindi]
सबसे शानदार फ़ोल्डेबल,
पल भर में फ़ुल चार्ज!
[Russian]
Чудо-
раскладушка с суперзарядкой!
[English (US)]
The ultimate foldable phone
instantly fully charged
with ultra-fast flash charging
[Korean]
역대급 폴더블폰!
눈 깜짝할 새
완충되는 초고속 플래시 충전!
[Dutch]
Snelste fold-laad
[Vietnamese]
Sạc siêu tốc, gập đỉnh cao
[Polish]
Ekspresowe ładowanie
[Indonesian]
Foldable tergokil, cas
kilat langsung penuh!