Welcome to the absolute pinnacle of modern,
uncompromised luxury real estate living right here today.
[Spanish (LATAM)]
Bienvenidos
a la cima absoluta de la vida moderna y
vida inmobiliaria de lujo sin concesiones,
hoy aquí.
[French (France)]
Bienvenue au sommet absolu du moderne,
l'immobilier de luxe sans compromis,
ici même aujourd'hui.
[German]
Willkommen am absoluten Gipfel
modernen, kompromisslosen Luxus-Wohnens
direkt hier bei uns heute.
[Italian]
Benvenuti
all'apice del moderno, lusso immobiliare
senza compromessi, qui e oggi.
[Portuguese (Brazil)]
Bem-vindo ao ápice absoluto do moderno,
o auge do luxo imobiliário, bem aqui hoje.
[Japanese]
現代の​極上の​暮らしの、
絶対的な​頂点へ​ ようこそ。
一切の​妥協​なき、
最高峰の​ラグジュアリー​邸宅です。
[Mandarin (Simplified)]
欢迎​来到​现代​住宅的​极致​巅峰
今天​为​您​呈现​毫无​妥协的​奢华​人居
[Arabic (Modern Standard)]
مرحباً بكم في قمة الحداثة المطلقة
في أرقى تجارب العقارات الفاخرة هنا واليوم
[Hindi]
आधुनिकता के परम शिखर पर आपका स्वागत
है, जहाँ आज आपको मिलेगा
बेमिसाल लक्ज़री रियल एस्टेट का अनुभव।
[Russian]
Добро пожаловать на вершину современного
бескомпромиссного элитного жилья,
представленного здесь и сейчас.
[Swedish]
Välkomna till höjdpunkten av modern,
kompromisslös lyx i fastighetsbranschen,
just här och nu.
[Korean]
현대적 인 주거의 정점에 오신
것을 환영 합니다.
타협 없는 럭셔리 부동산 라이프를 지금
바로 만나 보세요.
[Vietnamese]
Chào mừng đến với đỉnh cao tuyệt đối
của sự hiện đại,
xa hoa tuyệt mỹ hảo bất động sản xa hoa
hoàn mỹ ngay hôm nay.
[Polish]
Witamy na absolutnym szczycie
nowoczesności, bezkompromisowego luksusu
w nieruchomościach już dziś.
[Greek]
Καλώς ορίσατε στην απόλυτη
κορυφή του σύγχρονου,
αδιαπραγμάτευτης πολυτελούς διαβίωσης,
ακριβώς εδώ, σήμερα.